Jared Stefanowicz

STUDENT & SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

jaredStef@icloud.com (570) 472-5303 jaredstef.me Philadelphia, Pennsylvania

Profile

I'm a freelance software developer and student. I launched my first app as a sophomore in high school and have served many clients helping make their iOS app ideas a reality. I am currently studying Statistics with a minor in Mathematics at Temple University and am interested in fintech and quantitative finance.

Experience

Conference Assistant Temple University Conference Services

May, 2019 - August, 2019 Philadelphia, PA Assisted Temple University summer conference participants residing in university residence halls.

Intern CoalCreative.com

Jul 2017 – Nov 2017 Wilkes-Barre, PA Created websites using WordPress, HTML, and CSS. Attended meetings with clients and communicated progress updates on tasked projects.

Freelance iOS Developer Appitech LLC

Apr 2016 – Present Remote

Worked with multiple clients from start to finish making their app ideas a reality. Gained experience building client relations, managing expectations, price negotiations, and developing high quality, mission critical work in a time conscious manner.

Volunteering

Ambassador Student Voice

Aug 2017 – May 2018

Attended monthly meetings, wrote op-eds and guides, circulated petitions, spoke to school board at public meetings.

Junior Leadership Program Graduate Leadership Wilkes-Barre

Sep 2016 - May 2017

Planned and held charity event raising ~\$2k for non-profit Victory Sport. Spoke to newspapers and generated interest through social media ad campaigns while tasked as group treasurer and in charge of outreach.

Judge, iOS Development Speaker OwlHacks

March, 2019

Presented a 1-hour workshop titled "Intro to iOS Development" to hackathon students and helped judge submitted projects.

Education

Bachelor of Science Statistics, Minor: Mathematics 3.93/4 GPA

Fox School of Business at Temple University 2018 – 2022 (Expected)

Associate Technology Analyst - Fox Fund, Temple University Investment Association (TUIA), Johnson & Hardwick Residence Hall Community Council Vice President, Intramural Floor Hockey

HS Diploma

Hanover Area Jr/Sr High School 2014 – 2018 President Business Club, Senior Class Treasurer, Design Editor Yearbook, Voted most likely to succeed, Technology & Physics Department Award Winner

Awards

2nd - Vanguard ETF Trading Challenge Temple University

April, 2019

National Competitor - Securities & Investments FBLA

2018

1st Place - Computer Fair Programming Category LIU 18

2017, 2016

National Competitor - Intro. to Info. Technology FBLA

2016

1st Place Congressional App Challenge PA District 11

February, 2016

Projects

Hawk Bot Twitter Bot

August 2015 - June 2018

Coded Twitter bot in Java which tweeted the number of days left of school. Later the bot was rewritten in Python and scraped local news websites to automatically Tweet school closings and delays.

Skills

iOS Development (Swift & Objective C), Java SE, Python, JavaScript (Node.js), Tableau, MySQL